{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "A less formal document outlining mutual goals and cooperation established between two or more parties is referred to as:",
      "options": ["MOA", "SOW", "MOU", "MSA"],
      "correct_answers": ["MOU"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a global standard development organization composed of different national standards bodies?",
      "options": ["NIST", "ISO", "IEEE", "ANSI"],
      "correct_answers": ["ISO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"SD-WAN\" refers to a network technology that uses software to manage and optimize network connections that extend over large geographic areas.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a dedicated programming language used in database management?",
      "options": ["PHP", "C", "SQL", "JS"],
      "correct_answers": ["SQL"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following devices fall(s) into the category of PEDs? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": ["Smartphone", "Tablet", "Desktop", "Mainframe"],
      "correct_answers": ["Smartphone", "Tablet"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below is used to describe an average time required to repair a failed component or device?",
      "options": ["MTTF", "RPO", "MTTR", "MTBF"],
      "correct_answers": ["MTTR"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a firewall type that improves upon first- and second-generation firewalls by offering additional features, such as more in-depth inspection of network traffic and application-level inspection?",
      "options": ["IDS", "Packet filter", "NGFW", "Stateful firewall"],
      "correct_answers": ["NGFW"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which protocol enables secure, real-time delivery of audio and video over an IP network?",
      "options": ["S/MIME", "RTP", "SIP", "SRTP"],
      "correct_answers": ["SRTP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a network security technology designed to monitor, detect, and mitigate unauthorized access, security threats, and suspicious activities in WLANs?",
      "options": ["WIPS", "NIDS", "NIPS", "WIDS"],
      "correct_answers": ["WIPS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a method for creating and verifying digital signatures?",
      "options": ["DHE", "AES", "DSA", "SHA"],
      "correct_answers": ["DSA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A type of legally binding contract that establishes the foundational terms and conditions governing future agreements between two parties is known as:",
      "options": ["MOU", "SLA", "MSA", "SOW"],
      "correct_answers": ["MSA"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of IPsec provides authentication, integrity, and confidentiality?",
      "options": ["SPD", "PFS", "AH", "ESP"],
      "correct_answers": ["ESP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a multi-protocol authentication framework frequently used in 802.11 networks and point-to-point connections?",
      "options": ["PAP", "MS-CHAP", "EAP", "CHAP"],
      "correct_answers": ["EAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms represents evidence that helps cybersecurity professionals detect potential security incidents?",
      "options": ["APT", "IoC", "ATT&CK", "EDR"],
      "correct_answers": ["IoC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "For a wireless client to be able to connect to a network, the security type (e.g., WEP, WPA, WPA2, or WPA3) and encryption type (e.g., TKIP or AES) settings on the connecting host must match the corresponding wireless security settings on a WAP.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an obsolete authentication protocol that sends passwords in cleartext?",
      "options": ["PAP", "CHAP", "EAP", "MS-CHAP"],
      "correct_answers": ["PAP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an internal telephone exchange or switching system implemented in a business or office?",
      "options": ["POTS", "VoIP", "PBX", "PSTN"],
      "correct_answers": ["PBX"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a maximum tolerable period of time required for restoring business functions after a failure or disaster?",
      "options": ["SLA", "RTO", "AUP", "RPO"],
      "correct_answers": ["RTO"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A computer network connecting multiple LANs over an area of a city is called:",
      "options": ["PAN", "SAN", "MAN", "CAN"],
      "correct_answers": ["MAN"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cryptographic protocol is designed to provide secure communications over a computer network and is the successor to SSL?",
      "options": ["WEP", "CCMP", "TLS", "AES"],
      "correct_answers": ["TLS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an embedded microcontroller used for secure boot, disk encryption, and system integrity verification?",
      "options": ["TPM", "SoC", "UEFI", "HSM"],
      "correct_answers": ["TPM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to IMAP? (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Offers improved functionality in comparison to POP3",
        "Serves the same function as POP3",
        "Enables sending email messages from client devices",
        "Offers less functions than POP3",
        "Enables email exchange between mail servers"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Offers improved functionality in comparison to POP3",
        "Serves the same function as POP3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cryptographic solution would be best suited for low-power devices, such as IoT devices, embedded systems, and mobile devices?",
      "options": ["ECC", "DES", "RSA", "AES"],
      "correct_answers": ["ECC"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The term \"ASLR\" refers to a technique used in modern OSs to enhance:",
      "options": ["Data redundancy", "System security", "Performance", "Storage capacity"],
      "correct_answers": ["System security"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following solutions provide the AAA functionality? (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": ["CHAP", "TACACS+", "PAP", "RADIUS", "MS-CHAP"],
      "correct_answers": ["TACACS+", "RADIUS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a set of rules that specify which users or system processes are granted access to objects as well as what operations are allowed on a given object?",
      "options": ["CRL", "NAT", "BCP", "ACL"],
      "correct_answers": ["ACL"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A network admin can ping remote host by its IP address, but not by its domain name. Which of the following is the most probable source of this problem?",
      "options": ["ICMP", "DNS", "HTTP", "DHCP"],
      "correct_answers": ["DNS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The role of a RA in PKI is to: (Select 2 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Accept requests for digital certificates",
        "Validate digital certificates",
        "Authenticate the entity making the request",
        "Provide backup source for cryptographic keys",
        "Issue digital certificates"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Accept requests for digital certificates",
        "Authenticate the entity making the request"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a generic term used to identify any resource?",
      "options": ["OUI", "URI", "OID", "URL"],
      "correct_answers": ["URI"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a framework widely used for enabling secure third-party access to user accounts?",
      "options": ["SSO", "OAuth", "MFA", "SAML"],
      "correct_answers": ["OAuth"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An IV is a random or pseudorandom value used in cryptography to ensure that the same plaintext input does not produce the same ciphertext output, even when the same encryption key is used. The IV is typically used with encryption algorithms in block cipher modes to enhance security by introducing randomness to the encryption process.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a security vulnerability that allows an attacker to inject malicious code into input fields, such as search bars or login forms, to execute unauthorized commands on a database?",
      "options": ["RCE", "SQLi", "XSS", "CSRF"],
      "correct_answers": ["SQLi"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a mobile device deployment model in which employees select devices for work-related tasks from a company-approved device list?",
      "options": ["VDI", "CYOD", "BYOD", "COPE"],
      "correct_answers": ["CYOD"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms is used to describe sophisticated and prolonged cyberattacks often carried out by well-funded and organized groups, such as nation-states?",
      "options": ["MitM", "APT", "XSRF", "DDoS"],
      "correct_answers": ["APT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is STIX?",
      "options": [
        "Vulnerability database",
        "Common language for describing cyber threat information",
        "US government initiative for real-time sharing of cyber threat indicators",
        "Transport mechanism for cyber threat information"
      ],
      "correct_answers": ["Common language for describing cyber threat information"]
    }
  ]
}